<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Smart SpeakUp</string>
    <string name="user_name">Name: %1$s</string>
    <string name="user_email">Email: %1$s</string>
    <string name="user_mobile">Mobile: %1$s</string>
    <string name="error_parsing">Error parsing response!</string>
    <string name="error_fetching">Failed to fetch user details. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="user_not_found">User not found</string>
    <string name="invalid_user_id">Invalid user ID</string>
    <string name="about_app">Welcome to Our App!

Our app is your personal guide to improving English grammar and speaking skills. Whether you’re a beginner or aiming to refine your language abilities, this app is designed to help you communicate confidently and effectively.

How it Works:

1.Speak to the App: Using your phone’s microphone, you can speak directly to the app. Say sentences, phrases, or even have free-form conversations in English.
2.Speech Analysis: The app carefully listens to your input, identifies grammatical errors, and notes any pronunciation issues.
3.Instant Feedback: Once your speech is processed, the app highlights your mistakes and provides corrected versions in proper English.
4.Learn and Improve: Along with corrections, the app offers explanations and tips, helping you understand your mistakes and improve over time.

Why Use This App?
Our primary goal is to make language learning simple, interactive, and effective. With regular practice:

   You’ll improve your grammar and pronunciation.
   You’ll develop confidence in speaking English.
   You’ll receive constructive feedback tailored to your needs.
Whether you’re preparing for interviews, presentations, or everyday conversations, this app is a reliable companion for your learning journey.

Start Today:
Speaking is the key to mastering any language. Use the app daily, learn from your mistakes, and watch your English improve with every session.

Make English learning fun, easy, and accessible. Let’s help you speak with clarity and confidence!</string>

    <string name="feedback_header">Feedback!</string>
    <string name="email_hint">Your Email Address</string>
    <string name="query_hint">Write your query or feedback here...</string>
    <string name="submit_button">Submit</string>
    <string name="back">BACK</string>

    <string name="agora_channel">smarttalk</string>
    <string name="agora_temp_token">007eJxTYKjVsWOeEs5yLZA/6DTrVpVdKf9fsHcrZ7sVPZ9z46ZAd5cCg5mBZVpykqmRYZJpiomZsaVlclpyYqKJqVmaoaF5WmLKqthrGQ2BjAwX+ZcyMEIhiM/JUJybWFRSkpiTzcAAAH6/IPI=</string>
</resources>